**School Physicals & Immunizations:** Our dedicated team of health care professionals is here to provide comprehensive school physicals and immunizations, tailored to meet all school requirements and keep your child safe and healthy. **[Schedule an appointment](https://mychart.universityhealthsystem.com/MyChart/openscheduling/standalone?dept=10544001,10545001,10531001,10561001,10530001&vt=1003&view=group&public=1&highContrast=1).**

Close Alert Banner

* MAIN: [210-358-4000](tel:210-358-4000 "Main Phone Number")

* Site Search
    
     Search Site Search
    
    Please enter a search term

    * Search For a Doctor
        
         Search by name, specialty, or location Search

    * Search for a service
        
         Search by medical service or keyword Search

    * Search for a Location
        
         Search by name or service Search

* MAIN: [210-358-4000](tel:210-358-4000 "Main Phone Number")

* Site Search
    
     Search Site Search
    
    Please enter a search term

1. [Home](https://www.universityhealth.com/)
2. [Patient & Visitor Resources](https://www.universityhealth.com/patient-visitor-resources)
3. [Privacy Policies & Notices](https://www.universityhealth.com/patient-visitor-resources/privacy-policies-notices)
4. Website Privacy Policy

Website Privacy Policy
======================

Pages in this Section

Website Privacy Policy
======================

University Health respects the privacy of all those who visit our Web site and use our online services and will endeavor to implement measures designed to protect the privacy of those using our services. Note, however, that we do collect and use information from visitors to our Web site. This Web Site Privacy Policy sets forth our practices relating to the collection and use of information from you in connection with your visit to the University Health Web site and use of our online services.

Please be aware that University Health reviews its Web site privacy practices from time to time, and that those practices and this policy are, therefore, subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Web Site Privacy Policy. To contact University Health about Web site related privacy issues or to report a violation of our Web Site Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [Public.Relations@uhtx.com](mailto:Public.Relations@uhtx.com) with your request.

**Except as set forth within this Web Site Privacy Policy, we do not release personally identifiable information about our Web site visitors without their permission.**

**NOTE:** [University Health Notice of Privacy Practices](https://www.universityhealth.com/patient-visitor-resources/privacy-policies-notices/patient-safety) is a separate document that governs how medical information about you may be used and disclosed by University Health.

What Information Does University Health Collect From You in Connection With the University Health Web Site?
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* **Personally Identifiable Information**

> University Health collects and stores certain personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide to us in certain areas of our Web site, such as web pages that allow you to register for classes, provide us with input on our Web site, participate in on-line surveys or correspond with certain departments within the hospital (such as the Patient Relations department). Such information may include your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information (when applicable) and similar types of information. Although certain areas of the University Health Web site may require that you provide us with such personally identifiable information in order, for example, to complete certain on-line forms, you are free to use the remainder of the site without providing such personally identifiable information. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children (defined herein as minors younger than thirteen years of age) without obtaining parental consent. Before using the Site, we ask that children have their parents read this Web Site Privacy Policy.

* **Non-Personal Information**

> University Health also collects non-personal information such as web site usage, traffic patterns, site performance and related statistics based on our tracking of your visits to the Web site. Although such information is not personally identifiable, we can determine from an Internet protocol (IP) address a visitor's Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of his or her point of connectivity. We also use small text files placed on a user's computer hard drive ("Cookies") to help us determine the type of content and sites to which a visitor to the University Health site links, the length of time each visitor spends at any particular area of the University Health site and University Health services visitors choose to use. Cookies allow University Health to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience on University Health's Web site. Nevertheless, you should be able to control how and whether Cookies will be accepted by your Web browser. For more information on how to do so, please refer to the documentation accompanying your browser.

How We Use (and Do Not Use) the Information We Gather in Connection With the University Health Web Site?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Please take some time to familiarize yourself with the different ways University Health uses the information that it gathers. Keep in mind that, while University Health encourages all third parties involved – including but not limited to its affiliates and advertisers – to adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of our visitors and to otherwise handle personal information in a responsible manner, we cannot and do not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they use information received either from University Health or independently. Nevertheless, in the event that you encounter any third party associated with, or who claims association with, University Health who you feel is improperly collecting or using information about you, please contact [Public.Relations@uhtx.com](mailto:Public.Relations@uhtx.com) with your request. We will be happy to forward your message to the third party.

* **Personally Identifiable Information**

> University Health will use much of the personally identifiable information that you provide primarily for the purposes for which it was collected. For example, we will use information submitted for class registration to administer the classes and to notify you about class schedules and class information, information provided to the Patient Relations department will be used to respond to inquiries you have sent to the Patient Relations department, and information provided by on-line survey participants may be used to compile statistics regarding user preferences by geographic location. The personally identifiable information collected by University Health may also be used to improve the content of the Web site and to better address the needs and interests of Web site visitors. For example:
> 
> University Health may send its own e-mail solicitations to visitors who have not "opted out" of receiving such communications. The solicitations are limited in that they, among other things, will clearly indicate the originator of the e-mail and provide the customer with a method of "opting out" of receiving future communications of a similar nature.
> 
> Although University Health does not sell personally identifiable information about Web site visitors to third parties, we may, in certain circumstances, share personally identifiable information with third parties. For example, University Health may use third party service providers to facilitate our services and provide operations for one or more aspects of the University Health Web site. Such third party service providers may, in certain circumstances, require a visitor's personal information in order to facilitate our services and provide such operations. For instance, University Health uses a third party service provider for processing certain credit card transactions. Any credit card information submitted by you to University Health, therefore, will be submitted to our credit card processing service provider. If you decide that you would like to discontinue receiving promotional information from such third parties, please contact those third parties directly, or contact University Health at [Public.Relations@uhtx.com](mailto:Public.Relations@uhtx.com).
> 
> Notwithstanding anything herein to the contrary, we reserve the right to release information collected from a visitor (whether or not personally identifiable), including information contained within our access logs, when that visitor is in violation of our Terms of Use Agreement, or partakes (or is reasonably suspected of partaking) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant or other court order, and to release such information in response to court and governmental orders, civil subpoenas, discovery requests and as otherwise required by law. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. We also reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement individuals or entities for investigation or prosecution.

* **Non-Personal Information**

> University Health will use the non-personal information it collects in connection with your site usage for making changes or enhancements to the Web site and to better address the needs and interests of Web site visitors, as well as for other internal administrative purposes. We also may use data regarding site usage to determine which pages of the Web site are most helpful to visitors and to improve the information available through such pages. Further, we may provide statistical information based non-personal information to advertisers, affiliates and other current and potential business partners. We may also use aggregate data to inform these third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked on links to their Web sites. 

* **Use of Remarketing with Google Analytics**

> Analytics allows our website to automatically take advantage of new cross-device remarketing functionality now available in Google AdWords, which allows us to reach customers across devices when we use Google Analytics Audiences.
> 
> This feature allows us to reach previous website visitors with more relevant ads when they search or browse on another device. Users who have chosen to enable Google to associate their web and app browsing history with their Google account, and to use information from their Google account to personalize ads, Google will use data from its signed-in users together with our Google Analytics data to build audience lists for cross-device remarketing.
> 
> In order to support this feature, two things will happen: First, Google Analytics will collect Google-authenticated identifiers associated with users’ Google Accounts (and therefore, personal information). Second, Google Analytics will temporarily join these identifiers to our Google Analytics data in order to support our audiences.
> 
> AdWords remarketing will display ads to you based on what parts of the University Health website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your web browser.
> 
> This cookie does not in any way identify you or give access to your computer or mobile device.
> 
> The cookie is used to indicate to other websites that “This person visited a particular page, so show them ads relating to that page.”
> 
> Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.
> 
> If you do not wish to see ads from University Health you can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting [Google's Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated?hl=en).
> 
> You may also opt out of third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

What About Third Party Privacy Policies?
----------------------------------------

The University Health Web site contains links to other Internet Web sites, including co-branded or other affiliated sites which may or may not be owned or operated by University Health. University Health has no control, and is not responsible for, the privacy practices of other Web sites you may visit through links on the University Health Web site, including such sites' use of any information (such as IP number, browser type, or usage history) collected when visitors to the University Health Web site click through links to such sites. We recommend that you review individual Web site privacy policies before providing any information on such Web sites.

Last update: May 2017

4502 Medical Drive

San Antonio, Texas 78229

© copyright 2024 University Health. All rights reserved.
